

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

■ harry.bd11@gmail.com | HDonovan96 | MeachAbyss

# **Summary**

I am an avid programmer and passionate producer, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. My ideal position would be a Graduate/ Junior Producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience so I could progress to a more senior position.

### Skills

- · Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Jira, Trello
- · Version Control: Git
- · Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4
- Languages: C#, C++, Latex

# Education

### **Falmouth University**

BSc Computing For Games

· Worked with multi-discipline teams to bring several games through a full development cycle

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

# Published Games

#### Carma - Producer & Team Lead

Unity 2019.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)

- Published June 2021 · Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game
- Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile
- Removed blockers and streamlined development pipelines
- Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- Set up Steam store and maintained updated builds

#### Yvaga Station - Team Lead & Programmer

Unity 2018.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)

Published May 2020

- · Presented a concept pitch to in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Implemented asymmetric multiplayer game using PUN2 package for networking
- · Designed and implemented a modular custom movement system to expand on the options available to the player

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**Director** Falmouth, Cornwall

• Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing

**Senior Ambassador** 

**FXPLUS** 

GLASS NOMAD GAMES

Falmouth, Cornwall

March 2021 - Current

June 2020 - Current

- · Promoted from Student Ambassador
- Increased responsibility for the smooth running of events

· Handled registration and set up with services such as Steam

- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- · Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

# Programming Projects \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Boids Simulation** Unity 2019.4

## HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/HDONOVAN96/BOIDSSIMULATION

February 2021 - May 2021

- Investigated boids and optimisation methods
- · Implemented multithreading and spatial partitioning
- Pivoted to data-oriented rather than object-oriented implementation for performance

HARRY DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ JULY 23, 2021